(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-23T09:47:41.737550",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
世界で一番おひめさま
World's #1 princess!
そう言う扱い心得てよね
That's how you should treat me!
その一
Number one...
いつものと違う髪型に気付くこと
Notice when my hair is styled differently!
その二
Number two...
ちゃんと靴まで見ること
Check my shoes too, all the way!
いいね?
Got it?
その三
Number three...
わたしの一言には三つの言葉で返事すること
Reply to every word with three phrases!
わかったら右手がお留守なのをなんとかして!
If you understand, do something about my lonely right hand!
べつにわがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything,
キミに心から思ってほしいの
I just want you to truly believe from your heart
かわいいって
that I'm adorable!
世界で一番おひめさま
World's #1 princess!
気付いてねえねえ
Pay attention to me, hey, hey!
待たせるなんて論外よ
Making me wait is totally out of the question!
わたしを誰だと思ってるの?
Just who do you think I am?
もうなんだかあまいものが食べたい!今すぐに
I want some sweets right now!
欠点?かわいいの間違いでしょ文句は許しませんの
Faults? I'm just cute, no complaints allowed!
あのね わたしの話ちゃんと聞いてる?
Hey, are you even listening to me?
ちょっとあ、それとね?白いおうまさん
And hey, what about a white horse?
決まってるでしょ?迎えに来て
Come pick me up, obviously!
わかったらかしずいて手を引いて「おひめさま」って
Take my hand and say "My Princess"!
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world,
そういう扱い心得てよね
make sure you know how to treat me right.
その一 いつもと違う髪型に気づくこと
First, notice when I have a different hairstyle,
その二 ちゃんとお靴まで見ること
second, look all the way down at my shoes.
いいね?
Got it?
その三 わたしの一言には三つの言葉で返事すること
Third, reply to every word I say with three words.
わかったら右手がお留守なのをなんとかして!
If my right hand is empty, do something about it!
べつにわがままなんて言ってないんだから
I'm not saying I'm being selfish or anything,
キミに心から思ってほしいの かわいいって
I just want you to truly think I'm cute.
ちょっと!
Hold on...
あ、それとね 白いおうまさん 決まってるでしょ?
Ah, and the white horse should be a given, right?
迎えに来て
Come and pick me up!
わかったら かしずいて 手を取って おひめさまって
Take my hand and call me "Princess."
べつにわがままなんて言ってないんだから
I'm not saying I'm being selfish or anything,
でもね 少しぐらい叱ってくれたっていいのよ?
but you know, it's alright to scold me a little.
世界でわたしだけのおうじさま!
World's one and only princess!
きがつけて ねえてえ
Realize that, hey, hey.
おててが あいてます
Our hands are empty,
むくちで ぶあいそなおうじさま
reticent and blunt prince.
もう、どうして? きがついてよはやく
Why? Just notice it already!
ぜったい キミはわかってない!
You definitely don't understand!
いちごののったショートケーキ
Shortcake with a strawberry on top,
こだわりたまごのとろけるぷりん
pudding made with well-selected eggs.
みんな みんな がまんします...
Everyone holds themselves back for my sake...
わがままなこだと思わないで
Don't think that I'm just being selfish,
わたしだってやればできるもん
even I can do it if I try!
あとでこうかいするわよ?
You'll regret it later!
とうぜんです! だってわたしは
That's right, because I am...
世界で一番おひめさま!
the number one princess in the world!
ちゃんと聞いてる?ねえどこかに行っちゃうよ?
Make sure you listen closely,
ふいにだきしめられた きゅうにそんなえ??
Suddenly you held me tight, so abrupt, eh?
「ひかれるあぶないよ」そう言ってそっぽむくきみ
"It's dangerous," you say, turning away.
...こっちのがあぶないわよ!
...I think this person is dangerous though!
oh! hey baby!
Hey, baby!
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world,
そういう扱い心得てよね
make sure you know how to treat me right.
その一 いつもと違う髪型に気づくこと
First, notice when I have a different hairstyle,
その二 ちゃんとお靴まで見ること
second, look all the way down at my shoes.
いいね?
Got it?
その三 わたしの一言には三つの言葉で返事すること
Third, reply to every word I say with three words.
わかったら右手がお留守なのをなんとかして!
If my right hand is empty, do something about it!
べつにわがままなんて言ってないんだから
I'm not saying I'm being selfish or anything,
キミに心から思ってほしいの かわいいって
I just want you to truly think I'm cute.
世界でわたしだけのおうじさま!
World's one and only princess!
きがついているおててが あいてます
Realize that, look, look.
むくちで ぶあいそなおうじさま
Reticent and blunt prince,
もうどうして? きがついてよはやく
why? Just notice it already!
ぜったいわかってないわかってないわ
You definitely don't understand!
どこかに行っちゃうよ ふいにだきしめられた
Even if I were to go somewhere else,
きみはわかってないわかってないわ
you wouldn't understand!
いちごののったショートケーキ
Strawberry shortcake,
こだわりつめたこだわりたまごのとろけるぷりん
custard pudding with too much detail.
みんなみんながまんしますわがままなこだと思わないで
Everyone, everyone, I'm going crazy!
わたしだってやればできるもんあとでこうかいするわよ
If I do it myself, I can do it too.
とうぜんですだってわたしは世界で一番おひめさま!
I'm the number one princess in the world!
わあ... yeah!
Oh... yeah!
るなーい! みんなおるー!
Yay! Everyone, hello!
ほろらいぶ4期生 姫森るななのなーい!
This is Himemori Luna!
今日はなんと！
Today is, of course,
るなの誕生日ななのだーい！わーい！
Luna's birthday! Yay!
ということでね、今日は
So today,
こちらの姫森ルナ誕生日祭2022でいっぱいツイートしてほしいなだやー！
we're celebrating Himemori Luna's Birthday Live 2022!
そしてみんな
And everyone...
気になってると思うこのステージを紹介しちゃうなだやー！
you're curious about this stage, right?
まずは
First...
おる？ ルナイト？
Wait, is that Lunaito?
おまえ
Hey, you!
3Dになってんじゃねえかよ！
You became 3D, didn't you?!
おるルナイトちょっとこっち来いよ、ちょっとこっち来いよ。おいおいおい。
Hey Lunaito, come closer. Come closer.
ルナイト、おま、そこから動けるのかルナイト？でも見てかわいい！ルナイトやっと姫から3Dになったのね。
Look how cute Lunaito is, turned 3D for Luna!
また持って、そこでじゃあ見てほしいのならルナイト。
Come here, let everyone see you, Lunaito!
そして
And then...
え？なんだこれ？う、え？たこ焼きパパ？
What is this? Is it a Takoyaki Papa?
パパがさ、たくさんのさ、めりーごーらんど？
Papa, there are so many Takoyaki!
あ、なになにこれ？スピードが、え？パパ、パパ大丈夫？そのスピードついていけてる？
Papa, can you keep up with this speed?
パパ、やばい！これすげえのだ！めっちゃかわいいのだよ！
Papa, this is amazing! It's so cute!
笑っちゃ、笑っちゃいそうなんだけど、パパ大丈夫？めっちゃかわいい、めっちゃね、たこやきでね、
I can't stop laughing, but Papa, are you okay? It's so cute!
すごい作り込んでくれたんだよ！パパのお顔どうなっ、どうなってんだこれ？アップ、アップで、見、見れますか？
You put so much effort into making this! Papa, how's your face doing?
パパ！いつもの顔になったんだ！めちゃくちゃ可愛くね？このステージも作っていただいたのだよ！
Papa! You've got your usual face! That's so cute!
ライトもすげえのだ！走、走ってる！
The lights are amazing too! Look at them flashing!
みんな、こんにちは！
Hello, everyone!
ルナイトね、ルナイトね、パパもお祝いしてくれてるのね。
Look, Runights have prepared a carousel for me!
そして？
And then...
見て、お城！すごい！3Dの立体になってるのよ！見て、見て、見て！じゃじゃーん！
Look at the back! It's an incredible 3D castle! Look, look, look! Tada!
すっげえのよ！
Isn't it amazing?
え、あのへんルナイトのお部屋なのかな？
Is that Runight's room?
すごいすごいのよ！「Loyalty」って書いてあるでしょ？これもね、めっちゃかわいいのな！
It's so amazing! It says "Loyalty"! This is also super cute!
配信のね、スタンプで「LTL」「Loyalty to Luna」のね、そこからね、今日はこちらをタイトルにさせてもらったのよ！めっちゃかわいい！
It's from the streaming stamp "LT", "Loyalty to Luna", so today this became the title, it's super cute!
そして？
And then...
右の、えーと左の上のほうにさ、
On the upper right and left,
なんかルナイトの紋章が見えるのね！旗がね、はためいちゃってるのな！
I can see Runight's crests! Their flags are fluttering!
かわいい！ルナイトの紋章もね、こちらもね、かわいいのを作っていただきました！
So cute! Runight's crest and everything else, they made it so cute for us!
そして？
And then...
ちょっと待ってのよ。
Wait a minute.
え？え、ルナイト？お前、おまえ3Dになったのか？え、まさか、も、も、もっと！
Wait, Runight? You became 3D? No way, mo...
もてねえ！
Mote-nee!
動けるのな！
You're able to move!
ルナイト？ルナイトなの？
Runight? Runight, is that you?
ルナイト生きてんのかこれ？あ、動く！あ、ま、生きてんのか！生きてるよ、ルナイト！
Runight, are you alive? You're alive, Runight!
姫様、姫様！おまえ、と、と、と、と、ルナイトは3Dになりました！
Hime-sama, Hime-sama, Your majesty, Your majesty Runight became 3D!
おまえ喋れるのかよ！かわいい！
Can you speak? So cute!
パパがね、デザインしてくれた
Papa designed this!
こちらルナイトも、なんとね、今日のきのために3Dになってお披露目なのな！
This Runight became 3D for today and is greeting everyone!
今日はね、このルナイトたちと、怪獣パパと、この素敵なお城のね、ステージで
Today, with these Runights and Kaibutsu Papas, we're on this wonderful castle stage,
ルナたん歌って、踊って、踊って！いっしょに、おーまーまーだー！ゲストもね、たくさん呼んでいるので、最後まで楽しんでってほしいのな！
Let's sing, dance, and have fun together with our guests until the very end!
姫様！姫様！
Hime-sama! Hime-sama!
キミを見ていると いつもハートDOKIDOKI
Whenever I look at you, my heart always goes thump,
揺れる想いは マシュマロみたいにふわふわ
Like a marshmallow, my swaying feelings are light and fluffy.
いつもがんばる キミの横顔
Whenever you work hard, your diligent profile...
ずっと見てても 気づかないよね
Even if I keep looking, you don't notice.
夢の中なら 二人の距離縮められるのにな
Even if it's just a dream, I can close the distance between us,
あぁ カミサマお願いい
Ah, God, please,
二人だけのDream Timeください
Give me a Dream Time just for the two of us!
ふわふわ時間 ふわふわ時間 ふわふわ時間
Light and fluffy time, light and fluffy time, light and fluffy time.
お気に入りのうさちゃん抱いて 今夜もオヤスミ
Holding my favorite stuffed bunny, I'll go to sleep again tonight.
ふとした仕草に 今日もハートZUKIZUKI
With no time to even catch my breath...
さりげない笑顔を ふかぼりしすぎてOver heat!
Impulsively my heart throbs painfully again today.
いつか目にした キミのまじめ顔
Reading too much into your dry smile, I overheat!
瞳閉じても 浮かんできちゃうよ
Someday your serious face that I witnessed before
夢でいいから 二人のりSweet time欲しいの
Will come floating along even if I close my eyes.
あぁ カミサマどうして
Because it's okay in a dream, I want a Sweet Time between just the two of us.
好きになるほどDream nightせつないの
Ah, God, why...
とっておきのくまちゃん出だした 今夜は大丈夫かな？
Is it painful to fall head over heels in love during a Dream Night?
もう少し勇気ふるって 自然に話せば
As I bring the special stuffed bear, may it work well tonight?
何かが変わるのかな そんな気するけれど
If I show a little courage and talk naturally,
だけどそれが一番難しいのよ
I wonder if anything will change. I feel like that, but...
話のきっかけとかどうしよう
But that's the hardest part.
てか段取り考えてる時点で 全然自然じゃないよね
How do I find a chance to talk?
あぁもういいやねちおねちおねちおね
Y'know, by the time I think about what to say, it's completely unnatural.
あぁ カミサマお願い
Oh geez, no! Time to sleep, sleep, sleep~!
一度だけのMiracle timeください
O God, please, just this once give me a Miracle Time!
もしすんなり話せば そのあとは…どうにかなるよね
If I could say it smoothly, afterward... something or another will change.
ふわふわ時間 ふわふわ時間 ふわふわ時間
Light and fluffy time, light and fluffy time, light and fluffy time.
神戸 中央区 元町 （駅前）
Kobe Chuo-ku Motomachi (Station Square)
今日から ドキドキ ニーハオ ハロー ハン ユー 講座
Starting today, a thrilling Nihao, Hello, Hanyu course!
大人、中高生、おばあちゃんに「…こんにちは」
To adults, teens, and grannies: "...Hello."
「ダメダメ ここでは あなたも “ 喜歡 ” ！」
"No no, here you too must say 'Xi huan'!"
マジで…。テキスト 三ページ （早くも）
Seriously... Page 3 of the textbook (already!)
ここは とにかく 羞恥心 に 勝つ ぞ
Here, anyhow, we must overcome our shyness!
一万三千 円 の 月謝 は （安く ない ）
The 13,000 yen tuition (isn't cheap)
好好 大家 ご機嫌 かな （ 媽 媽 ）
Hao hao dajia, how are you? (Māma)
「ここはどこ 君は誰」 （ 你 是 誰 阿 ）
"Where is this, who are you?" (Nǐ shì shuí a)
大好きな ワン・リーホン に 大好きだって 言う ため
To tell my beloved Wang Leehom I love him,
ハイハイ チャイナ ちょっと 夢心地 いーあるふぁんくらぶ
High-high China, a dreamy little I-aru Fanclub!
だんだん 君と同じ 言葉 が 使える ね
Gradually, I can use the same words as you,
うおあいにー 言える かな
I wonder if I can say "Wo ai ni."
そこで 知り合った 女子高生 （ みかちゃん ）
A high school girl I met there (Mika-chan)
謳う、台湾で ジェイ・チョウ の コンサート
Claims there's a Jay Chou concert in Taiwan—
それは 行かなきゃ だめ だ （ ところで ）
We just have to go! (By the way,)
みかちゃん しれっと 言ってる けど 海外 だよ ？
Mika-chan says so casually, but that's overseas!
まじで…。エンジン かかってん な （ みかちゃん ）
Seriously... You're really getting into it (Mika-chan).
ここは とにかく 便乗 して 頑張る か
Anyway, I'll just hitch a ride and do my best!
六万 数千 の 旅費 も （ 安く ない ）
The 60,000-some-odd travel costs (aren't cheap)
それでは 再見 バイト 探さ なく ちゃ
So then, Zàijiàn, I've got to find a part-time job!
「すみません、お嬢さん」 （ 小姐 ）
"Excuse me, young lady" (Xiǎojiě)
「これ 一つ いくら でしろう」 （ 多少 錢 ）
"How much is one of these?" (Duōshǎo qián)
天国 の レスリー・チャン に おやすみなさいって 言う ため
To tell Leslie Cheung in heaven, "Good night,"
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Los! Achtung! Deckung! Hinlegen! Halt!
戦場へ！前線へ！そして死の淵まで！
To the battlefield! To the front lines! To the abyss of death!
命捨てたその覚悟を示せ！
Show your resolve to cast your life aside!
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Los! Achtung! Deckung! Hinlegen! Halt!
聴こえるだろう　あの砲声が
You can hear that artillery fire, can't you?
抵抗する蟷螂の声音だ
It's the defiant voice of a mantis.
踏み潰せ！踏み潰せ！
Trample them down! Trample them down!
諸君、我々の任務は何だ
Gentlemen, what is our mission?
殲滅だ！
Extermination!
一機残らずの殲滅だ！
Total extermination down to the last one!
為すべきことは唯一つ
There is only one thing to be done:
地獄を創れ！
Create hell!
何故炎の中進んで行くのか　弾丸の雨に打たれに行くのか
Why do we march through the flames, walking into a rain of bullets?
笑止千万！帝国(くに)の為だ！
Utterly absurd! For the empire!
戦場へ！前線へ！そして死の淵まで！命捨てたその覚悟を示せよ！
To the battlefield! To the front lines! To the abyss of death! Show your resolve!
忠誠を！従順を！そして其の魂を全て捧げ勝鬨を上げよ！
Pledge your loyalty, obedience, and soul, and raise a shout of victory!
さあ此処に築いてみせろ！天に届く死体(ひと)の山を！
Now build here for all to see a mountain of corpses reaching the heavens!
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Los! Achtung! Deckung! Hinlegen! Halt!
どこに恐怖があると言うんだ
Where is there any fear to be found?
見ろ　血肉が花火の様だ
Behold, flesh and blood are like fireworks!
撒き散らす　撒き散らす　千の傷跡
Scattering, scattering a thousand scars!
忘れちゃいけないさ
You must not forget them:
炎の熱も　零れた腑臓も
The heat of the flames, the spilled viscera,
最後の呻きも　濁った瞳も
The final moan, the clouded eyes—
哀訴、それこそを求めるのだ！
Begging for mercy, that is what is desired!
安寧も平穏も増えて和解なんて気の沙汰は　地獄よりも楽園の様だ
Peace, calm, and reconciliation sound more like paradise than hell!
その四肢は踊る為　踊り狂う為有る趣なのだ！
Those limbs exist only to dance, to dance in a frenzy!
人間に価値など無い　価値無き者同士の争いに命の徒花を咲かせてみせろ！
Human life has no value—let a fruitless flower of life bloom in conflicts between the valueless!
法律も秩序でも狂った奴が創ってる　まさに笑劇(ファルス)　不条理だけの起承転結
Laws and order are made by the mad—a true farce, a sequence of pure absurdity!
戦場へ！前線へ！そして死の淵まで！命捨てたその覚悟を示せよ！
To the battlefield! To the front lines! To the abyss of death! Show your resolve!
忠誠を！従順を！そして其の魂を全て捧げ勝鬨を上げよ！
Pledge your loyalty, obedience, and soul, and raise a shout of victory!
さあ此処に築いてみせろ！天に届く死体(ひと)の山を！
Now build here for all to see a mountain of corpses reaching the heavens!
Feuer! Sperrfeuer! Los! Achtung! Deckung! Hinlegen! Halt!
どこに恐怖があると言うんだ
Where is there any fear to be found?
見ろ　血肉が花火の様だ
Behold, flesh and blood are like fireworks!
撒き散らす　撒き散らす　千の傷跡
Scattering, scattering a thousand scars!
忘れちゃいけないさ
You must not forget them:
紅い蜥蜴も　枯れたルピナス
The red lizard, the withered lupine,
登っていく荊の声だ
It's the voice of climbing thorns.
踏み潰せ　踏み潰せ　鮮烈の傷跡は忘れちゃいけないさ
Trample them, trample them! You must not forget those vivid scars!
僅暗い熱も　零れた腑臓も　最後の呻きも　濁った瞳も
The dim heat, the spilled viscera, the final moan, the clouded eyes—
絶望の泥を吐き出した狂気の沙汰は　地獄よりも楽園のようだ
This madness spitting out the mud of hell is more like paradise!
その死しは踊る為　踊り狂う為有るのだ
That death exists to dance, to dance in a frenzy!
忠誠を！従順を！そしてその魂を全て捧げ起死回生を上げよ
Pledge your loyalty, obedience, and all your souls, and raise a cry of revival!
さあそこに気付いて見せろ！天に届くリートの山にこだまする
Now notice it and show it—echoing on the mountain of lead reaching to the heavens,
憎しみさえかき消す発砲を　狂おしいほどに
Gunfire that drowns out even hatred, madly so!
戦場へ！前線へ！そして死の淵まで！命捨てたその覚悟を示せよ！
To the battlefield! To the front lines! To the abyss of death! Show your resolve!
起死回生を！そしてその魂を！全て捧げ起死回生を上げよ！
Raise a cry of revival! Pledge your soul and raise a cry of revival!
さあそこに気付いて見せろ！天に届くリートの山にこだまする
Now notice it and show it—echoing on the mountain of lead reaching to the heavens,
肉しみさえかき消す発砲を　解き放て　発砲を！
Gunfire that drowns out even hatred—release the gunfire!
戦場へ！前線へ！そして死の淵まで！命捨てたその覚悟を示せよ！
To the battlefield! To the front lines! To the abyss of death! Show your resolve!
起死回生を！そしてその魂を！全て捧げ起死回生を上げよ！
Raise a cry of revival! Pledge your soul and raise a cry of revival!
さあそこに気付いて見せろ！天に届くリートの山にこだまする
Now notice it and show it—echoing on the mountain of lead reaching to the heavens,
肉しみさえかき消す発砲を　解き放て　発砲を！
Gunfire that drowns out even hatred—release the gunfire!
こちら、幸福安心委員会です。
[Kochira, Koufuku Anshin Iinkai desu.]
どうして みんなが幸せななの?
Why is everyone so happy?
この世界のこと 聞きたいって 知りたいって
Wanting to hear about this world, wanting to know about it,
水辺の公園で みんなが耳をすませて
At the lakeside park, everyone is straining their ears,
わくわくするね ねぇ、オンディーヌ?
It's so exciting, right, Ondine?
ハイ、ハイッ!
Hi-hai!
さあさあみなさん 教えてあげます!
Come on, everyone, I'll teach you all about it!
みんなが気になっていること 疑問に思っていること
Everything you're worried about and wondering about,
ぜーんぶ教えてあげます!
I'll teach you the whole thing!
我々幸福安心委員会は みなさまの幸せを願い、そして支えます!
We, the Happiness and Peace of Mind Committee, wish for your happiness and support you!
幸福なのは 義務なんです
Happiness is an obligation.
幸せですか? 義務ですよ?
Are you happy? It's an obligation, you know?
幸福なのは 義務なんです
Happiness is an obligation.
幸せですか? 義務ですよ?
Are you happy? It's an obligation, you know?
ですから、安心して義務を果たすように!
Therefore, be at ease and fulfill your obligation!
みなさまの幸せが 我々の幸せ。
Everyone's happiness is our happiness.
幸せですか? 義務ですよ?
Are you happy? It's an obligation, you know?
果たしてますか? 幸せじゃないなら...
Have you fulfilled it? If you're not happy...
絞首、斬首、銃殺、釜茹で、歴史、電気、火炙り、生埋め、薬殺、石打ち、鋸、張り付け
Hanging, beheading, firing squad, boiling, exile, electrocution, burning, burial, lethal injection, stoning, sawing, crucifixion...
好きなのを選んでね!
Choose whichever you like!
ハイ、ハイッ!
Hi-hai!
さあさあみなさん 幸せだけが満ちてます!
Come on, everyone, only happiness fills this place!
不安とか不満、何ひとつないでしょう?
There isn't a single anxiety or dissatisfaction, is there?
こわい、こわいわ! 幸せすぎて、こわいわ!
It's scary, so scary... It's so happy, it's scary.
本当に みんなが幸せなの?
Is everyone really happy?
この世界のそと 行きたいって逃げたいって
Wanting to go outside of this world, wanting to escape,
水辺の公園で みんなが耳をふさいで
At the lakeside park, everyone was covering their ears
びくびくしてた ねぇ、オンディーヌ?
and trembling in fear, right, Ondine?
ハイ、ハイッ!
Hi-hai!
さあさあみなさん 死にましたー!
Come on, everyone, they died!
オンディーヌを振った騎士は死にましたー!
The knight who rejected Ondine has died!
葬儀に出るなら 向こうに並べ! それ以外は幸せに暮らせ!
If you're attending the funeral, line up over there! Everyone else, live happily!
幸福なのは 義務なんです
Happiness is an obligation.
幸福なのは 義務なんです 幸せですか? 義務ですよ?
Happiness is an obligation. Are you happy? It's an obligation, you know?
幸福なのは 義務なんです
Happiness is an obligation.
幸福なのは 義務なんです 幸せですか? 義務ですよ?
Happiness is an obligation. Are you happy? It's an obligation, you know?
義務なんです 義務ですよ? 義務なんです 幸福なのは 義務なんです
It's an obligation, it's an obligation, you know? It's an obligation, happiness is an obligation.
義務なんです 義務ですよ? 義務なんです 幸福なのは 義務なんです 幸せじゃないなら... 死ね
It's an obligation, it's an obligation, you know? It's an obligation, happiness is an obligation. If you're not happy... die.
さあ行くよ! ワン! ツー! スリー!
Here we go! One! Two! Three!
桃色片想い 恋してる
A peach pink crush, I'm in love
あ、いくよ… ワン！ツー！スリー！
Ah, let's go... One! Two! Three!
桃色の片想い 恋してる
Pink unrequited love, I'm in love
マジマジと見つめてる
Staring intently
チラチラって目が合えば 胸がキュルン
When our eyes meet, my heart flutters
桃色のファンタジー 片想いらしい片想いなんて
Pink fantasy, a true unrequited love like this
初めてしちゃいます
is a first for me
わかんない事がわかんないくらい 好きみたいで
I like you so much I don't even know what I don't know
あの人には 恋人いるかな
I wonder if that person has a lover
夢にだって 出てきちゃいいます
He even appears in my dreams
今以上 気になっちゃう
Making me care about him even more
桃色の片想いしちゃってる
I'm deep in a pink unrequited love
知らぬ間にしちゃってる
Falling into it without even realizing
偶然に出会えて 胸がキュルン
We met by chance, my heart flutters
桃色の片想い 恋してる
Pink unrequited love, I'm in love
マジマジと見つめてる
Staring intently
チラチラって目が合えば 胸がキュルン
When our eyes meet, my heart flutters
桃色のファンタジー
Pink fantasy
誘えない とても誘えない 緊張しちゃいます
I can't ask him out, I can't possibly ask him out, I get so nervous
わかってる そうね わかってる ここがこくるときね
I know, yes I know, it's time to confess
桃色の片想い 恋してる
Pink unrequited love, I'm in love
マジマジと見つめてる
Staring intently
偶然に出会えて 胸がキュルン
We met by chance, my heart flutters
桃色のファンタジー
Pink fantasy
桃色の片想い 恋してる
Pink unrequited love, I'm in love
マジマジと見つめてる
Staring intently
チラチラって目が合えば 胸がキュルン
When our eyes meet, my heart flutters
胸がキュルン
My heart flutters
桃色のファンタジー
Pink fantasy
誘えない とても誘えない 緊張しちゃいます
I can't ask him out, I can't possibly ask him out, I get so nervous
わかって そうね わかって ここが告る時ね
I know, yes I know, it's time to confess
きあい入れて 話かけましょう
Let's pump ourselves up and talk to him
勇気出して 「こんにちは」「しるし」さようなら～ 会話になってない…
Gathering my courage: "Hello", "See you", "Goodbye" — that's not even a conversation...
桃色の片想いしてるけど
I've got a pink unrequited love, but
両想いめざすけど
I want you to feel the same, but
きのうより ちかづいた
We've gotten closer than yesterday
胸がキュルンン
My heart is thumping
桃色の片想い kissしてる
I'm in a pink unrequited love, kissing you
夢みてる
Dreaming away
あなたにはみえますか？
Can you see it?
恋の色が
The color of love is
桃色の季節
Pink season
桃色のファンタジー
Pink fantasy
わんわんわんわんわんわんわんわん
Woof woof woof woof woof...
恋びといるのかな
I wonder if you have a lover
夢にだって出てきちゃう
You even appear in my dreams
今以上 気になっちゃう
Making me care about you even more
桃色の片想い 恋してる
Pink unrequited love, I'm in love
マジマジと見つめてる
Staring intently
チラチラって目が合えば 胸がキュルン
When our eyes meet, my heart flutters
桃色のファンタジー
Pink fantasy
桃色の片想い 恋してる
Pink unrequited love, I'm in love
マジマジと見つめてる
Staring intently
チラチラって目が合えば 胸がキュルン
When our eyes meet, my heart flutters
桃色のファンタジー
Pink fantasy
うっせぇわ
Shut up, shut up, shut the hell up!
ちっちゃな頃から優等生
I was an honour student being young
気付いたら大人になってた
Before I realized, I was already grown up
ナイフのような思考回路
A train of thought like a knife
持ち合わせる訳もなく
Which I didn't have that with me
でも遊び足りない 何か足りない
But I'm not having enough fun, something is missing
困っちまう これは誰かのせい
These troubles better be somebody's fault
あてでもなくただ混乱するエディイ
I'm just confused today
それもっか最新の流行は当然の把握
Understanding the latest trends
経済の動向も通勤時チェック
Checking the stock market on my way to work
純情な精神で入社ワーク
Joining a company with the pure spirit
社会人じゃ当然のルールです
These are the obvious rules for us workers
うっせえわ
Usseewa
正しさとは 愚かさとは
What is rightness? What is stupidity?
それが何か見せつけてやる
I will show you what they are.
ちいさな頃から優等生
I was an honor student since I was little.
気づいたら大人になっていた
Before I knew it, I was already grown up.
ナイフのような思考回路
A train of thought like a knife,
持ち合わせる訳もなく
Which I didn't have with me,
でも遊び足りない 何か足りない
But I'm not having enough fun, something is missing.
困っちまうこれは誰かのせい
These troubles better be somebody's fault.
あてもなくただ混乱するエイデイ
I'm just confused every single day.
それもそっか
Well, is that so?
最新の流行は当然の把握
Understanding the latest trends naturally,
経済の動向も通勤時チェック
Checking the economy on my commute,
純情な精神で入社しワーク
Joining work with a pure spirit,
社会人じゃ当然のルールです
These are the obvious rules for workers.
はぁ? うっせえ うっせえ うっせえわ
Huh? Shut up, shut up, shut the f*** up!
あなたが思うより健康です
I'm healthier than you think.
一切合切凡庸な あなたじゃ分からないかもね
You are too mediocre to understand me, perhaps.
ああよく似合う その可もなく不可もないメロディー
Ah, that ordinary melody suits you so well.
うっせえ うっせえ うっせえわ
Shut up, shut up, shut the f*** up!
頭の出来が違うので問題はナシ
I deal with things differently so no problem at all!
ついつい私模範人間
I'm an exemplary person after all.
殴ったりするのはのーせんきゅー
Punching someone is a no-thank-you.
だったら言葉の銃口をその頭に突き付けて撃てばマジヤバない? 止まれやしない
If I pointed my words at your head and fired, wouldn't that be crazy? I can't stop.
不平不満垂れて成れの果てサディスティックに変貌する精神
Complaining until you drop dead, my spirit becomes sadistic.
クソだりいな 酒が空いたグラスあればすぐに注ぎなさい
I'm f***ing tired. Pour drinks when glasses are empty.
皆が摘み易いように串外しなさい
Take off the skewers so everyone can eat easily.
会計や注文は先陣を切る
Take the lead in ordering and paying the bill.
不文律最低限のマナーです
These are the minimum rules for social manner.
はぁ? うっせえ うっせえ うっせえわ
Huh? Shut up, shut up, shut the f*** up!
くせぇ口塞げや限界です
Close your stinking mouth, I've reached my limit.
絶対絶対現代の代弁者は私らぐらいもう見飽きたわ
I'm fed up with those modern spokespersons repeating the same rehash.
二番センジ言い換えのパロディ
A second-rate parody of rewritten words.
うっせえ うっせえ うっせえわ
Shut up, shut up, shut the f*** up!
まるまるとにくさいついたその面前にバツ
Draw an 'X' on that fat, smug face of yours.
うっせえ うっせえ うっせえわ
Shut up, shut up, shut the f*** up!
うっせえ うっせえ うっせえわ 私が生きている俗に言う天才です
Shut up, shut up, shut the f*** up! I'm the so-called genius alive!
うっせえ うっせえ うっせえわ
Shut up, shut up, shut the f*** up!
あなたが思うより健康です
I'm healthier than you think.
一切合切凡庸なあなたじゃ分からないかもね
You are too mediocre to understand me, perhaps.
ああつまらんね
Ah, so boring.
何回聞かせるんだそのメモリー
How many times do I have to hear those memories?
うっせえ うっせえ うっせえわ
Shut up, shut up, shut the f*** up!
あたしもたいがいだけどどうだっていいぜ問題はナシ
I know I'm not a big deal either, but I don't care, no problem at all!
うっせえ うっせえ うっせえわ
Shut up, shut up, shut the f*** up!
私家族で言う天才です
I'm a genius according to my family.
うっせえ うっせえ うっせえわ
Shut up, shut up, shut the f*** up!
あなたが思うより健康です
I'm healthier than you think.
一切合切凡庸な あなたじゃ分からないかもね
You are too mediocre to understand me, perhaps.
ああつまらんね 何回聞かせるんだそのメモリー
Ah, so boring. How many times do I have to hear those memories?
うっせえ うっせえ うっせえわ
Shut up, shut up, shut the f*** up!
あたしも大概だけどどうだっていいぜ問題はナシ
I know I'm not a big deal either, but I don't care, no problem at all!
よみがえれ
Revive...
空と大地が 交差している
The sky and the earth are crossing paths.
今 佇んでる この世界で
In this world where I stand now,
命が生まれ また沈んでく
Life is born and then fades away.
繰り返される 営みの中
In the endless flow of time,
こんなものよぎった瞬間 夢は力をなくす
When things get tough like this, dreams lose their strength.
もう一度 生まれよう この場所で
Let's be born again right here!
正義の その奥で 夢が息づいている
Deep within justice, dreams are alive.
重なる 力を信じて
Believing in the power that overlaps,
正義の その奥で 闇が潜んでいる
Deep within justice, darkness is lurking.
見極めろ 全てを
See it all clearly.
振り上げた 剣は切り裂くためじゃない
The raised sword isn't meant just to cut things down.
引き合う絆で 呼び覚ませ 鮮やかに
With the bonds we share, wake up, vividly.
傷ついて 行き場を なくし
Wounded and lost,
さまよって いる その魂を
Wandering in turmoil...
癒やす力は 心の奥で 静かに鼓動を刻んでいる
The power to heal lies deep in the heart, quietly carving out a path.
持てる力 全てぶつけ 涙を流す のなら
Smash through all the power you have if you're going to shed tears.
選ぶべき 道は 君を待っている
The city you should choose is waiting for you.
見失った 今と 通り過ぎた 過去の 狭間で あきらめる よりも
Rather than giving up in despair over the past,
今 目をそらさずに ここからはじめよう 見極めろ 明日を
Let's start fresh from here without looking away. See tomorrow clearly.
誰かに 見せつける 勇気は 脱ぎ捨てて
Cast aside the courage you show to others,
素顔に戻ろう 呼び覚ませ 鮮やかに
And return to your true self, wake up, vividly.
正義の その奥で 夢が息づいている
Deep within justice, dreams are alive.
重なる 力を信じて
Believing in the power that overlaps,
正義の その奥で 闇が潜んでいる 見極めろ 全てを
Deep within justice, darkness is lurking. See it all clearly.
振り上げた 剣は切り裂くためじゃない
The raised sword isn't meant just to cut things down.
引き合う絆で 呼び覚ませ 鮮やかに
With the bonds we share, wake up, vividly.
よみがえれ
Revive...
空と大地が交差している
The sky and the earth cross paths.
今たたずんでいるこの世界で
In this world where I stand now,
命が生まれまた沈んでく
Life is born and then sinks away.
繰り返される繁みの中
In the repeating cycle of bustling life...
こんなものとヨギった瞬間 夢は力をなくす
Dreams lose their power in the moment you realize it's just this.
もう一度生まれようこの場所で
Let's be born once more in this place.
正義のその奥で夢が息づいている
Deep within justice, dreams are breathing life.
重なる力を信じて
Believing in the overlapping power...
正義のその奥に闇が潜んでいる
Deep within justice, darkness is lurking.
見極めろ全てを
See everything clearly!
振り上げた剣は切り裂くためじゃない
The raised sword isn't meant for cutting things down,
引き合う絆で呼び覚め鮮やかに
Wake up vividly through the intertwined bonds!
傷ついて行き場をなくし
Wounded and losing my way,
さまよっているその魂を
wandering souls...
癒やす力は心の奥で静かに鼓動を刻んでいる
The power to heal beats quietly deep in the heart.
let there be light revive a soul
曲がりくねり はしゃいだ道
Twisting and turning, this winding road,
青葉の森で駆け回る
running through the forest of green.
遊びまわり 日差しの街
Playing around in the sunlit town,
誰かが呼んでいる
someone is calling out.
夏が来る 影が立つ
Summer comes, shadows grow,
あなたに会いたい
I want to meet you.
見つけたのはいちばん星
I found the brightest star.
明日も晴れるかな
Will tomorrow be sunny, too?
パプリカ 花が咲いたら
Paprika, when the flower blooms,
晴れた空に種を蒔こう
we'll scatter the seeds in the clear sky.
ハレルヤ 夢を描いたなら
Hallelujah, if you painted a dream,
心遊ばせあなたに届け
let your heart play and reach you.
雨に燻り 月は陰り
The rain falls and the moon hides,
木陰で泣いていたのは誰
who was crying under the trees?
一人一人慰めるように
As if comforting each other one by one,
誰かが呼んでいる
someone is calling out.
喜びを数えたら あなたでいっぱい
When I count the joys, you fill my heart,
帰り道を照らしたのは 思い出の影ぼうし
and shadows of memories lit the way home.
パプリカ 花が咲いたら
Paprika, when the flower blooms,
晴れた空に種を蒔こう
we'll scatter the seeds in the clear sky.
ハレルヤ 夢を描いたなら
Hallelujah, if you painted a dream,
心遊ばせあなたに届け
let your heart play and reach you.
会いにゆくよ 並木を抜けて
I'll run to you, through the forest we played,
歌を歌って
singing our song.
手にはいっぱいの花を抱えて
I filled both my hands with flowers for you.
ララルリルラ
La-loo la-ri-da,
会いにゆくよ 並木を抜けて
I'll run to you, through the forest we played,
歌を歌って
singing our song.
手にはいっぱいの花を抱えて
I filled both my hands with flowers for you.
ララルリルラ
La-loo la-ri-da,
パプリカ 花が咲いたら
Paprika, when the flower blooms,
晴れた空に種を蒔こう
we'll scatter the seeds in the clear sky.
ハレルヤ 夢を描いたなら
Hallelujah, if you painted a dream,
心遊ばせあなたに届け
let your heart play and reach you.
かかとお弾ませ この指とまれ
Bounce your heels and join in with me!
引き裂いた 闇が吠える 震える帝都に
When the howling darkness is rent asunder and the capital trembles,
愛の歌 高らかに 踊り出る戦士たち
we soldiers leap out, making the air ring with a love song.
心まで 鋼鉄に 武装する乙女
We are maidens armed with steel down to our hearts,
悪を蹴散らして 正義をしめすのだ
scattering the forces of evil to show the way to justice!
走れ 光速の 帝国華撃団
Run, fast-as-light Imperial Floral Assault Force!
唸れ 衝撃の 帝国華撃団
Roar, electrifying Imperial Floral Assault Force!
私たちは 正義のために戦います たとえそれが命をかける戦いであっても
We fight for justice, even if we must risk our lives in that fight—
私たちは一歩も引きません それが帝国華撃団なのです！
we won't back down a single step! That's the Imperial Floral Assault Force!
街の灯が 消え果てて 怯える帝都に
When the city lights have gone out and the capital is afraid,
虹の色 染め上げて 踊り出る戦士たち
we soldiers leap out, painting the sky in rainbow colors.
暁に 激情を 照らし出す乙女
We are maidens who light up the dawn with our passion,
悪を滅ぼして 正義をしめすのだ
wiping out the forces of evil to show the way to justice!
走れ 光速の 帝国華撃団
Run, fast-as-light Imperial Floral Assault Force!
唸れ 衝撃の 帝国華撃団
Roar, electrifying Imperial Floral Assault Force!
走れ 光速の 帝国華撃団
Run, fast-as-light Imperial Floral Assault Force!
唸れ 衝撃の 帝国華撃団
Roar, electrifying Imperial Floral Assault Force!
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の胸の奥まで届くようなメロディ 奏でるよ
Happy Synthesizer! I'll play a melody that reaches deep into your chest.
儚く散った 淡い片想い 笑い話だね 今となれば
My fleeting, faint unrequited crush is just a funny story now.
見る物全て輝いて見えた あの日々が綺麗に笑ってるよ
Back when everything I saw shone bright, those days are smiling so prettily.
我慢することだけ覚えなきゃいけないの? 「大人になって頂戴ね」ならなくていいよ
Do I only need to learn to hold back? If that's being "grown-up," I don't want it!
知らない言葉ばかり 知らないなんて言えなくて 大変お似合いで 嘘ついてごめんね
Full of words I didn't know, too embarrassed to admit it, I lied—sorry!
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の胸の奥まで届くようなメロディ 奏でるよ
Happy Synthesizer! I'll play a melody that reaches deep into your chest.
つまらない「たてまえ」や ヤナ事全部 消してあげるから この音で
Boring pretense and things you hate, I'll wipe them all away with this sound!
何の取り柄もない ぼくに唯一少しだけできること
With no special talents of my own, it's the one small thing I can do.
心躍らせる 飾らない言葉 電子音で伝えるよ
Heart-exciting, unadorned words, I'll convey them through electronic sound!
好きになること 理屈かなんかじゃなくて こじつけなんていらないじゃない
Falling in love isn't about logic; we don't need far-fetched excuses, right?
時代のせいとあきらめたらそこまで
If you give up and blame the times, that's where it ends.
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の胸の奥まで 届くようなメロディ 奏でるよ
Happy synthesizer, playing a melody
that reaches deep into your heart.
僅か散らかった淡い片思い 笑い話だね 今となれば
A slightly messy, faint unrequited love,
a funny story now looking back.
見る物全て輝いて見えてた あの日々がキレイに笑ってるよ
Everything shone brightly,
those days are smiling so cleanly.
我慢する事だけ覚えなきゃいけないの?
Do I only need to learn to hold back?
「大人になって頂戴ね?」 ならなくていいよ
"Please grow up to be an adult?"
You don't have to become one.
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の胸の奥まで 届くようなメロディ 奏でるよ
Happy synthesizer, playing a melody
that reaches deep into your heart.
つまらない「たてまえ」やヤな事全部 消してあげるから この音で
Boring pretenses and all unpleasant things
I'll erase them with this sound.
何の取り柄も無い 僕に唯一少しだけ出来る事
With no special merits, the only thing
I can do just a little bit
心揺らせる 飾らない言葉 電子音で伝えるよ
Is to convey unadorned words
that shake your heart through electronic sounds.
好きになる事理屈なんじゃなくて 「こじつけ」なんて要らないんじゃない?
Falling in love isn't about logic,
we don't need far-fetched excuses.
時代のせいに諦めたらそこまで 踏み出さなくちゃ何も始まらない
If you give up blaming the times, that's it.
You must step forward for anything to begin.
「ゴメンね夜遅く寝るとこだったでしょ?」
"Sorry for calling so late, were you going to bed?"
「驚いた私もかけようとしてた」
"I was surprised, I was about to call you too."
ハッピーシンセサイザ ほらね 楽しくなるよ 涙拭うメロディ 奏でるよ
Happy synthesizer, see how it gets fun?
Playing a melody to wipe away tears.
強がらなくたっていいんじゃない? 別に自分に素直になればいい
You don't have to act tough, do you?
Just be true to yourself.
何の取り柄も無い 僕に唯一少しだけ出来る事
With no special merits, the only thing
I can do just a little bit
ちょっと照れるような 単純な気持ち 電子音で伝えるよ
A simple feeling that makes me a bit shy,
I'll convey through electronic sounds.
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の胸の奥まで 届くようなメロディ 奏でるよ
Happy synthesizer, playing a melody
that reaches deep into your heart.
つまらない「たてまえ」やヤな事全部 消してあげるから この音で
Boring pretenses and all unpleasant things
I'll erase them with this sound.
何の取り柄も無い 僕に唯一少しだけ出来る事
With no special merits, the only thing
I can do just a little bit
心揺らせる 飾らない言葉 電子音で伝えるよ
Is to convey unadorned words
that shake your heart through electronic sounds.
ハッピーシンセサイザ ほらね 楽しくなるよ 涙拭うメロディ 奏でるよ
Happy synthesizer, see how it gets fun?
Playing a melody to wipe away tears.
強がらなくたっていいんじゃない? 別に自分に素直になればいい
You don't have to act tough, do you?
Just be true to yourself.
何の取り柄も無い 僕に唯一少しだけ出来る事
With no special merits, the only thing
I can do just a little bit
ちょっと照れるような 単純な気持ち 電子音で伝えるよ
A simple feeling that makes me a bit shy,
I'll convey through electronic sounds.
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の胸の奥まで 届くようなメロディ 奏でるよ
Happy synthesizer, playing a melody
that reaches deep into your heart.
つまらない「たてまえ」やヤな事全部 消してあげるから この音で
Boring pretenses and all unpleasant things
I'll erase them with this sound.
何の取り柄も無い 僕に唯一少しだけ出来る事
With no special merits, the only thing
I can do just a little bit
心揺らせる 飾らない言葉 電子音で伝えるよ
Is to convey unadorned words
that shake your heart through electronic sounds.
みんない、みんない！ここまでどうだったー？
Everyone, everyone! How was it up to here?
去年MCね、ほとんどなしでね、ずっと歌いっぱなし、踊りっぱなしで来たんだけど
Last year there was almost no MC,
just singing and dancing the whole time,
うんうんうんうん。
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
そう、気づいたのら？今日はね、いつもねライブにお呼びするゲストではなく、珍しいねゲストを呼ばせていただきました！
That's right, did you notice?
Today we invited quite a rare guest instead of the usual ones!
まず最初はねおかゆと歌って、次あーちゃんと歌って、あまにゃんとも歌って、ポルポルとも歌って、まあいつものしゅばもいるけどね。
First we sang with Okayu, then A-chan,
Amanyan, Polpol, and our usual Subaru too.
でもね、なかなかない珍しいメンバーでね歌ったと思うんだけどみんなどうだったのら？
We sang with a pretty rare and unusual lineup,
how did everyone like it?
うんうんうんうん。いいよね！なんかたまにはこういうのもいいと思うのらね！なんかねちょっといつもとは違うメンバーで歌って、あなたもすごく楽しかったなら、みんな来てくれてね、ありがとね！
Yeah, yeah! It's nice! Doing this once in a while
is great! If you had fun singing with different members,
thank you so much for coming!
そして！ここでねなんと！お知らせがあります。まずは1つ目！誕生日記念グッズが出てまーす！
And now! We have an announcement here!
First off, number one! Birthday commemoration merch is out!
ででん！お、かわいい！なんかもうすでに可愛いので溢れているのらね！なんだのらこれ？
Ta-da! Oh, cute! It's already overflowing
with cuteness! What is this?
まずは1つ目！
First one!
ででん！かざきぱっぱかきおろしな、B2タペストリーなのら！
Ta-da! A B2 tapestry with brand-new artwork
by Kazaki Pappa!
こちらはなんとね、ルナたんの新衣装を着てね、トゥルーナイトであるみんなに指輪をね、捧げているところなのだよ！めっちゃかわいいのだー！
Here, wearing Luna-tan's new outfit,
she's dedicating a ring to all her True Knights!
It's super cute!
そして！ででん！そのトゥルーナイトの証である、誓約の指輪！
And! Ta-da! The proof of being a True Knight,
the Oath Ring!
こちらもね、ルナたんの王冠にね、お星様、みかづき、あ、ルナたんの剣も付いてる！すごい可愛いね！デザインにしていただきました！こちらね首から下げるチェーンも付いているのでね、ぜひね使ってほしいのだな！
This also has Luna-tan's crown, a star, crescent moon,
ah, Luna-tan's sword too! It's super cute!
It comes with a chain to hang around your neck!
そして！こちら！ルナたんの髪の色とおそろ！ルナ色のタンブラーなのだな！
And! This one! Matching Luna-tan's hair color!
A Luna-colored tumbler!
ルナたんの顔もね、プリントされているのでね、こちらもね、みんな使ってほしいのだな！
Luna-tan's face is also printed on it,
so I want everyone to use this too!
そして！ででん！チャーム付きスマホリング！
And! Ta-da! A smartphone ring with a charm!
こっちもめちゃくちゃかわいいのだ！
This one is super cute, too!
お揃いに、身につけるのに、もうあれ？
To match, to wear, wait...
チェーンも付いてるからね、こちらね、チャームが付いてるからみんなこれ取り外ししてね
It comes with a chain and charm so you can detach it
バックにつけることもできるしね、スマホリングとしてね、使ってほしいのだ！
and attach it to your bag, or use it as a smartphone ring!
そして、
And,
こちらフルセットでね、ご購入いただいた方には、ルナたんの直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入り、かんざきパパ描き下ろしのポストカードをお届けします！
for those who purchase the full set, we'll deliver a postcard drawn by Kanzaki-papa, featuring Luna-tan's autograph and foil-stamped message!
みんなぜひね、ご購入してみてくださいね！
Everyone, please be sure to check it out!
そして、もう一つお知らせがあります。
And I have one more announcement.
なんと！ルナたんのオリジナル新曲、第2弾！本日の24時に各種音楽サイトでリリースされるのだ！
Guess what! Luna-tan's 2nd original song will be released on music sites tonight at midnight!
ではね、最後にお披露目したいと思います。それでは聞いてください、ぐるぐる@まわる@まわるルナ！
Now, I'd like to unveil it at the end. Please listen to "Guruguru@Mawaru@Mawaru Luna"!
ぐるぐるまわる まわるルナ
Guruguru mawaru mawaru Luna
まわる まわる とまわる ルナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning around, Luna
まわる まわる まわる ルナ ルナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning, Luna, Luna
まわる まわる まわる ルナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning, Luna
まわる まわる 地球を ぐるぐる
Spinning, spinning, the Earth goes round
またたく間に 街中が
In the blink of an eye, the town
まわる まわる 頭クラクラ
Spins and spins, making my head dizzy
幕が上がり 祭りの始まり
The curtain rises, the festival begins
盤れ舞えれ 眉を開いたら
Dance and whirl, open your eyes wide
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる回って (もっともっと)
spin around even more (More and more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
みんなぐるぐるぐるる回って (もっと)
everyone spin round and round (More!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる回って (もっともっと)
spin around even more (More and more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
ずっとぐるぐるぐるる まわるルナ (やぁ！)
keeping on spinning, spinning Luna! (Yay!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って
Laugh, laugh, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる笑って (もっともっと)
laughing even more (More and more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 踊って
Dance, dance, round and round,
みんなぐるぐるぐるる踊って (もっと)
everyone dancing round and round (More!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる そうやって
Just like that, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる回って (もっともっと)
spin around even more (More and more!)
ずっとぐるぐるぐるる まわるルナ (やぁ！)
keeping on spinning, spinning Luna! (Yay!)
回り過ぎたら 世界の闇が
If we spin too much, the world's darkness
みんなを包む 恐怖乱舞
will wrap around everyone in a frantic dance
大丈夫 守るから
It's okay, I will protect you
ぐるぐる 地球は回り始め幾億年 いつまでも このまま回る みんなに幸せを まわりつづく まわるルナ
For hundreds of millions of years the Earth keeps spinning round and round, spinning on forever to bring happiness to everyone, spinning Luna
ますますます社会がぐるぐる
Society spins round and round more and more
まーぁれ！？ (わぁ！)
Huh?! (Whoa!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる回って (もっともっと)
spin around even more (More and more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
みんなぐるぐるぐるる回って (もっと)
everyone spin round and round (More!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる回って (もっともっと)
spin around even more (More and more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
ずっとぐるぐるぐるる まわるルナ (やぁ！)
keeping on spinning, spinning Luna! (Yay!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って
Laugh, laugh, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる笑って (もっともっと)
laughing even more (More and more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 踊って
Dance, dance, round and round,
みんなぐるぐるぐるる踊って (もっと)
everyone dancing round and round (More!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる そうやって
Just like that, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる笑って (もっともっと)
laughing even more (More and more!)
ずっとぐるぐるぐるる まわるルナ (やぁ！)
keeping on spinning, spinning Luna! (Yay!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる回って (もっともっと)
spin around even more (More and more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
みんなぐるぐるぐるる回って (もっと)
everyone spin round and round (More!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる回って (もっともっと)
spin around even more (More and more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin, spin, round and round,
ずっとぐるぐるぐるる まわるルナ (やぁ！)
keeping on spinning, spinning Luna! (Yay!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って
Laugh, laugh, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる笑って (もっともっと)
laughing even more (More and more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 踊って
Dance, dance, round and round,
みんなぐるぐるぐるる踊って (もっと)
everyone dancing round and round (More!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる そうやって
Just like that, round and round,
もっとぐるぐる回って (もっともっと)
spin around even more (More and more!)
ぐるぐるまわる まわるルナ！ (やぁ！)
Spinning around, spinning Luna! (Yay!)
Loyalty to Luna Himemori Luna Birthday Live
Loyalty to Luna - Himemori Luna Birthday Live -